[Music]
[音乐]
at its very simplest Tomcat is a web
最简单的Tomcat是Web服务器，可以在此基础上进行一点扩展
server to expand on that a little bit
there are a series of Java
有一系列Java规范定义了一种
specifications that define a way that
web applications can be written and
可以编写Web应用程序，而Tomcat实现这些规范
Tomcat implements those specifications
and it's one of a number of servers that
它是众多服务器的其中之一，因此Web应用程序开发人员可以
do so a web application developer can
write their web application using the
使用标准API编写其Web应用程序，然后就可以在
standard API and then it can run on
Tomcat it can run on jetty it can run on
Tomcat，可以在Jetty上运行，可以在WebSphere上运行，可以在WebLogic和
WebSphere it can run on WebLogic and
because it's the same interface the same
因为在任何地方都可以移动相同的界面和相同的标准
standard everywhere you can move your
application from one to the other and it
从一个应用程序到另一个应用程序，它将可以正常工作，但是最简单
will just work but at its simplest
Tomcat is a way of running websites is
Tomcat是一种运行网站的方法，与Apache Web完全分开
completely separate from the Apache web
server however if you wish you can get
服务器，但是，如果您希望，您可以使两者进行某种合作
the two to sort of working cooperation
so one of the things that Tomcat doesn't
因此，Tomcat本身内部不做的一件事就是负载概念
do within itself is the idea of load
balancing so if you've got more load
进行平衡，因此如果您的负载超过一台物理服务器无法处理的负载
than one physical server can't handle
and you need to spread it between
您需要将其分散在多个对象之间
multiple ones you need something to
spread that load what we often see
分散负载我们经常看到人们正在做的事情就是将Apache网站
people doing is putting Apache web
server in front of it because it can do
服务器在它前面，因为它可以进行负载平衡，然后坐在
the load balancing and then it sits in
front of Tomcat and it spreads the load
Tomcat的前端，它将负载分散到不同的Tomcat实例之间
between the different Tomcat instances
and then brings the responses back
然后将响应汇总在一起，然后发送给用户
together and sends them off to the users
and we have quite close cooperation
而且我们在Tomcat项目的各个部分和
between bits of the Tomcat project and
bits of the Apache web server project
Apache Web服务器项目的一部分，因为我们有效地拥有了自己的
because we have effectively our own
protocol that we use to do some of that
我们用来进行某些通信的协议，因此我们共同致力于新的
communication so we work together on new
features developing that integration of
开发整合功能的功能我专注于您的特定功能
that I am focused on your particular
projects so I am currently a committer
项目，因此我目前是PMC的提交者和比索的成员
PMC member and a member of the peso
software foundation I have been that for
我从事软件工作很长一段时间，一直致力于
a long time I've been a committer for
the camel product for yeah as I said
我说过的骆驼产品大约是12年，我目前的角色是
about 12 years my current role is as a
professional open source developer I'm
我受雇于red的专业开源开发人员
employed by red
and redhead uses camel in in the middle
和红发在我们的产品中间使用骆驼，所以我目前
of our products so I am currently
heavily involved with camel their camel
大量参与骆驼活动的骆驼基本上是用于整合
is basically used for integration is to
switch I mean I for integration
开关我的意思是说，我参加了集成高科技大会吗？
hi-c algunas ation do they have so many
different IT systems and they need to be
不同的IT系统，它们需要集成在一起，您需要知道数据
integrated connected you know it data
need to be transfer from different
需要从不同的系统转移，其中有很多，所以有很多
system many of them so there are so many
different protocols languages and IT
不同的协议语言，IT系统和操作系统以及
systems and operating systems and
whatnot and data formats and camel is
whatnot和数据格式以及骆驼有点像介于两者之间的胶水
sort of like the glue that sits between
and you can easily more easily integrate
您可以更轻松地集成它们，我从更多系统开始
them I started with more system
integration so more project related to
集成，因此有更多与应用程序运行时相关的项目，因此可以运行一些
application runtimes so running some
stuff and application easily for you and
东西和应用程序很容易为您提供许多功能，您可以
providing a lot of features you can
leverage so I started with this kind of
杠杆，所以我从Apache这样的项目开始，现在我仍在从事
project Apache now I'm still working on
this project still very happy and and
这个项目仍然很开心，是的，这仍然是我的项目，但是我
and yeah it's still my project but I
like a lot I'm also working on big data
像很多人一样，我也在开发与大数据相关的产品，像Apache这样的大数据
related products so big data like Apache
carbon data for instances is a database
碳数据实例是为大数据设计的数据库，我真的很高兴
designed for big data I'm really happy
about this product because it's one of
关于这个产品，因为这是我做过的第一个项目
the first project that I did with
Chinese guys and it was really great
中国人，我正在研究的大数据真的很棒
around big data I'm also working on
Apache beam which is a very key project
Apache Beam是一个非常关键的项目，提供了针对以下语言的API
providing an API for a language that
allows you to design some big data
允许您设计一些大数据管道或分布式处理
pipelines or distributed processing of
data so this project historically on
数据，因此该项目历来在哪个项目上进行
which are working on another project
which is nama Apache you know me is more
那是纳玛·阿帕奇，你知道我更多关于用户配置文件，gdpr之类的东西
about user profiling and gdpr and stuff
like that and the thing that I really
这样，我真正喜欢的东西之间存在某种联系
like is there some connection between
all these products the connection is
所有这些产品的连接是一些项目用户之间的联系
between some project user others for
example you know me is based on Apache
例如，您知道我基于Apache Cara，而Apache Cara是我所负责的项目之一
Cara which is one of project arm I'm
working on for a long time beam using
使用扫射和火花对光束进行长时间工作，因此有很多
fling and spark so there are a lot of